https://www.arentwenaughty.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

We use cookies to make your experience better. To comply with the new e-Privacy directive, we need to ask for your consent to set the cookies. Learn more.Allow Cookies
Menu Home CategoriesSex ToysSex Toys for HerVibratorsVibrating PantiesRabbit VibratorsBullet VibratorsFinger VibratorsThrusting VibratorsDildosPussy PumpsBreast and Nipple ToysKegel ExercisersPulsatorsClitoral StimulatorsSex Toys for HimSex DollsCock RingsVibrating Cock RingsMen's MasturbatorsPocket PussyPenis PumpsPenis SleevesPenis ExtensionsPenis EnlargersSex Toys for CouplesBondage (BDSM)Sex FurnitureCondomsKitsBody Paints and PowdersStrap-Ons and HarnessesCouples VibratorsLubes
Gels
Sprays and OilsAphrodisiacsMassage OilsDesensitizersLubesArousal GelsBath and Shower GelsKitsAdult Novelties and BooksSex GamesAdult Novelty GiftsParty SuppliesSex BooksClothing & AccessoriesLingerieBikinisDressesCostumesCorsets and TeddiesBody JewelryMale LingerieAccessoriesShoesWigsAnal ToysAnal BeadsButt PlugsVibratorsCleansingElectro StimulationStimulatorsKitsAccessoriesMassageMassage WandsAccessoriesSex Toy AccessoriesSex Toy StorageToy CleanersSupplements and EnhancementsFor HerFor HimCharging
Batteries
etc. Brands About Us Contact Stores Account Settings Currency CAD - Canadian Dollar GBP - British Pound Sterling EUR - Euro INR - Indian Rupee USD - US Dollar
Privacy and Cookie Policy
We will never sell, share, or divulge your email address and/or other personal information that we collect for the purposes of your order.
Aren’t We Naughty has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering & dissemination practices for this web site: ArentWeNaughty.com
Use of this website's order form requires users to give us contact & shipping information (like their name, address & email address), & financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). The customer's contact information is used to contact the customer when necessary.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse & alteration of the information under our control.
We have a security SSL certificate which encrypts sensitive information being sent over the Internet. Our servers are located in a world-class data center located at 151 Front Street in Toronto, Canada's premiere technology facility and carrier hotel.
Our site also employs the use of MasterCard SecureCard and Verified by Visa (VbV) security protocols. For more information about these services, please visit the links below.
• MasterCard SecureCode• Verified by Visa
All credit card orders are processed through TD Online Mart service. All debit card orders are processed by your financial institution website. We do not see or store any customer's payment card information.
Cookies
By using ArentWeNaughty.com, you understand that we do not collect any personal information that may be used to identify you unless you provide it to us.
By visiting this website, you understand that third-party advertisers and analytics providers may collect unidentifiable information about your browsing activities across this and other websites in order to offer more tailored ads to you that better suit your shopping needs.
If you would like to opt-out of third party advertising which is used only to deliver better ads to you as the consumer, please click here and select “Google Inc.”
In order for the site and the online shopping cart to work properly, you must still allow your browser to accept cookies from our website. Cookies from ArentWeNaughty.com are used to facilitate your shopping experience.
This privacy policy sets out how this website (hereafter "the Store") uses and protects any information that you give the Store while using this website. The Store is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. The Store may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by letting us know using our Contact Us information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us this request using our Contact Us information.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
Cookie NameCookie Description
FORM_KEY
Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.
PHPSESSID
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to view and edit their orders.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
SECTION-DATA-IDS
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
X-MAGENTO-VARY
Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
All     Sex Toys for Her       Vibrators         Vibrating Panties         Rabbit Vibrators         Bullet Vibrators         Finger Vibrators         Thrusting Vibrators       Dildos       Pussy Pumps       Breast and Nipple Toys       Kegel Exercisers       Pulsators       Clitoral Stimulators     Sex Toys for Couples       Bondage (BDSM)       Sex Furniture       Condoms       Kits       Body Paints and Powders       Strap-Ons and Harnesses       Couples Vibrators     Anal Toys       Anal Beads       Butt Plugs       Vibrators       Cleansing     Adult Novelties and Books       Sex Games       Adult Novelty Gifts       Party Supplies       Sex Books     Clothing & Accessories       Lingerie       Bikinis       Dresses       Costumes       Corsets and Teddies       Body Jewelry       Male Lingerie       Accessories       Shoes       Wigs     Sex Toy Accessories       Sex Toy Storage       Toy Cleaners     Massage       Massage Wands       Accessories     Electro Stimulation       Stimulators       Kits       Accessories     Supplements and Enhancements       For Her       For Him     Lubes
Gels
Sprays and Oils       Aphrodisiacs       Massage Oils       Desensitizers       Lubes       Arousal Gels       Bath and Shower Gels       Kits     Charging
Batteries
etc.     Sex Toys     Sex Toys for Him       Sex Dolls       Cock Rings         Vibrating Cock Rings       Men's Masturbators         Pocket Pussy       Penis Pumps       Penis Sleeves       Penis Extensions       Penis Enlargers
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies. However you may visit Cookie Settings to provide a controlled consent.
Cookie Settings Accept
